wellpoint.com 2017-02-02

# Privacy

#### **Web Privacy Statement**

Your privacy is very important to us and we will make every reasonable effort to safeguard any information we collect.

 **  
What information will we collect?**

Information may be collected in the following ways on this website:

We may use “cookies” to help us improve this website by tracking your navigation habits and to store some of your preferences. A cookie is a small file created by a website to store information on your computer. Cookies do not allow websites to gain access to other information on your computer. Once a cookie is saved on your computer, generally only the website that created the cookie can read it.

An Internet Protocol address is a number that automatically identifies the computer or mobile device that you are using to access the Internet. The IP address enables our server to send you the site pages that you want to visit or the data you want to view. The IP address may disclose the server owned by your Internet service provider. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to support our site administration.

 **How will information be used?**

In addition to the uses described above we may also gather quantitative user information, such as the number of users and the pages or data accessed, in order to perform administrative, technical, hosting or other functions that help us manage our website and deliver new functionality to you. We do not sell, license, transmit or disclose personal information collected by this site except when required or permitted by law.

 **Third Party Service Providers**

We may work with third party service providers who may place third party persistent cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to collect anonymous information about the use of our websites. They are not permitted to collect any personal information, and this information will be solely used for web usage analysis for a better understanding of how you use our website, and/or to customize our content and advertising.

 **What if I don’t want information about me to be collected?**

If you do not wish to have your activity on our website tracked, [you can opt-out at any time here](http://www.112.2o7.net/optout.html?second=1) to discontinue first party cookie tracking of your web activity.

You also have the choice to opt-out of third party cookies, web beacons or similar technologies, if you do not want third party service providers to collect your anonymous information for marketing purposes, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to perform the opt-out.

Additionally, you can direct your Internet browser to notify you and seek approval whenever a cookie is being sent to your hard drive. You may also delete a cookie manually from your computer, tablet or smartphone through your Internet browser settings or other programs. You can also set your browser to refuse all cookies. Please note that some parts of this website may not function properly or be available to you, if you refuse to accept a cookie or choose to disable the acceptance of cookies.

 **“Do Not Track” Signals**

We do not respond to web browser “do not track” signals. As such, your navigation of our site may be tracked as part of the gathering of quantitative user information described above. If you arrive at our website by way of a link from a third party site that does respond to “do not track” requests, the recognition of any “do not track” request you have initiated will end as soon as you reach our site.

 **Linking to Other Sites**

From time to time we will provide links to websites not owned or controlled by us. We do this because we think this information might be of interest or use to you. While we do our best to ensure your privacy, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. A link to a third party website does not constitute or imply endorsement by us. Additionally, we cannot guarantee the quality or accuracy of information presented on those websites. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of any website you visit.

 **Use of electronic mail**

We may provide email links to facilitate communication between us and you. Information collected through email may be shared with our customer service department, employees or third parties that perform services on our behalf. Unless otherwise noted, email through our website is not a completely secure and confidential means of communication. Non-encrypted email may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users without your knowledge and permission while in transit to us.

 **Contacting the Privacy Office**

Anthem’s Privacy Office is available to answer privacy questions or for reporting privacy issues. You may contact the Privacy Office by writing us at the following address:

Privacy Office: OH0101-C300 4361 Irwin Simpson Road, Mason, OH 45040

e-Mail Anthem’s Privacy Office: Privacy.Office@anthem.com

This privacy statement is effective December 1, 2014. This privacy statement is subject to change. We encourage you to review it from time to time.
